module.exports = [
 {
   question: 'Which pair of colors are complimentary?',
   a: 'Red and blue',
   b: 'Red and orange',
   c: 'Purple and orange',
   d: 'Purple and yellow',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'What year was Toy Story released?',
   a: '1995',
   b: '1996',
   c: '1997',
   d: '1998',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'What century was the Mona Lisa painted in?',
   a: '15th Century',
   b: '16th Century',
   c: '17th Century',
   d: '18th Century',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'Van Gogh painted for only 9 years of his life. How many artworks did he create in that time?',
   a: '450',
   b: '860',
   c: '1,550',
   d: '2,100',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which famous person did Annie Leibovitz photograph the day that he was later killed?',
   a: 'Steve McQueen',
   b: 'Selena',
   c: 'John Lennon',
   d: 'Biggie Smalls',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'Who is the author and illustrator of Where the Wild Things Are?',
   a: 'Eric Carle',
   b: 'Maurice Sendak',
   c: 'Ludwig Bemelmans',
   d: 'Shel Silverstein',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'Beyonce is the most grammy-nominated woman in history. How many noms has she received?',
   a: '37',
   b: '48',
   c: '63',
   d: '71',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which color does the human eye process first?',
   a: 'Yellow',
   b: 'Green',
   c: 'Blue',
   d: 'Red',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'What were the colors of the Women\'s Suffrage movement?',
   a: 'Purple, Yellow & White',
   b: 'Purple, Green & White',
   c: 'Purple, Pink & Green',
   d: 'Purple, Yellow & Green',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'What is the name of Tina Belcher\'s vocal group in Bob\'s Burgers?',
   a: 'The Shirley Tempos',
   b: 'The Hormone-iums',
   c: 'Pitch Slapped',
   d: 'The Unaccompanied Minors',
   answer: 'b'
 },
];